Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The exam to join the ranks of the Magic Knights, the elite squad to protect the Clover Kingdom under the command of the Wizard King, was underway in the Royal Capital.
In the final stage of the exam, candidates are pitted against each other to assess their combat skills and observe how they use their grimoires in battle.
Now! Beacon! No pulling punches, remember? Let's do this, Asta! Ha ha!
Bronze Creation Magic! Seke Magnum Cannonball!
What do you think of this, Captains? The bronze magic power I've crafted is dual purpose.
It protects me and attacks with magic bullets. It will fend off his pathetic attack, showing off my skills at defense.
Then, the second he's exhausted, I'll go on the offensive and shoot!
Come on, don't get shy on me now! Ha ha!
どなた!
Sustainable my body
中央 未尽味 どこまでも 幅かけたら な いつの日も 夢見てた それでも一歩一歩しかしかな 世界でも なんでも香り立てそう 本能のまま 諦めしたいからさ
apos
遥か未来へ 今 駆け出したんだ
まだ見ぬ白腕ずら 全て超えて
あの日描いた 僕が僕であるために
いつの日数 Increase of your Palmer
君と言う希望と
まるでいつかのワンページのような
Just met you with me
We should travel vem up
Well this is done bad
Some kid from the Stix doesn't have a power to get past that
Man, I wish I'd've been the one to take him on
Ha! And did get a look at that tattered ol' grimoire of his?
I mean, seriously, do you think he can even use magic?
And no one from nowheresville.
No chance any squad's gonna make an offer for him.
Come on, don't get shy on me now.
Good. Watching him struggle should liven things up.
Okay, here we go.
He's quick. Fast transportation magic.
No magical enhancements there.
This kid is just in crazy good shape.
Unlike you, Seke.
I'm not joining the magic knights just so I can slack off and have a little fun.
I've got a much bigger goal.
I'm gonna be the Wizard King.
That grimoire.
Hey.
He's not the one who will defeat you, Oster.
I am.
Is that a magic sword?
So he's not just some poor reject from the Styx.
What's his deal?
Who is he?
And that stuff he said about the Wizard King?
That's right, you heard me!
I'm gonna become the Wizard King, you got it?
They're a problem with that?
He's officially nuts.
Him, the Wizard King?
Talk about delusions of grandeur.
He's so out of touch with reality.
I almost feel sorry for the guy.
Withdraw already, you dumb kid!
Who are you calling a dumb kid?
Hmm.
More creation magic, I'd wager.
Impressive moves.
Based on the other tests, I would have never expected him to have that much magic power.
Yeah, well, he didn't use magic power.
I mean, it's not so much that he didn't use it.
More like, he doesn't have it.
Matter of fact, I didn't pick up on any mana before.
But he's saying he's gonna be the Wizard King?
Huh.
We got ourselves a real odd duck here.
Hmm.
THE END
Wow, watching Nobles fight is something else.
Between their raw power and their training, they're unstoppable.
Whoa, so cool!
Seeing the show these two are putting on makes me think that a runt from before was nothing to write home about.
Right? The other guy was just careless, that's all.
What was your name? Oh yes, Yuno was it?
Well, looks like you don't have a sparring partner yet.
Perhaps you would like to take me on then.
Hey, isn't that...
Yeah, it's Salim, from the Hapshass family.
You may have been chosen by the Four Leaf Clover, but you're still a mere commoner.
I'll show you just how superior we nobles are to your kind in rank and power.
Oh, and wealth too, obviously.
Now, begin!
Having the opportunity to battle the great Salim de Hapshass, that alone is quite an honor.
It will give you something to talk about when you return to your little village.
You won't go empty-handed. Take this as a souvenir.
A special nobles move I call Holy Lightning Rising Salim!
Yuno?
I've arranged for your transportation home!
Wind magic. Towering tornado!
Why isn't nobody here?
What the tales of money are you boys?
No!
Who____ء!
окаezo.
Where are you boys from?
Ha!
He totally flattened a noble!
I can't believe it!
Whoa!
He's really good.
I wonder if he'd like to be our friend.
Wow!
A good showing.
Yeah.
That concludes the exam.
When your number is called, please step forward to learn your results.
If a captain wants you on his or her squad, they will raise a hand.
That means you're in.
If you do not wish to join a squad, you may, of course, decline.
If you are admitted into more than one squad, it is up to you to decide which you will join.
However, if no squad wants you, you will not be a magic knight.
In which case, you must leave at once.
Examinee No. 1, step forward.
Uh, yes, sir!
No. 32, no hands.
No. 40, no hands.
No. 45, no hands.
No. 67, no hands.
No. 41, no hands.
Come on.
First raised hand.
Lucky.
Number 71, the Purple Orcas.
Number 78, we'll take this one.
The Crimson Lion Kings.
Number 99, the Coral Peacocks.
Number 116, no hands.
Oh, man.
Number 141, no hands.
Yeah, that's pretty much what I expected.
Well, I guess the fields back home won't till themselves.
This is intense.
Next.
Number 164, here.
You know.
Do we have any hands?
No way.
All of them?
It's impossible.
Has that ever happened?
I guess it's not just royalty and nobles who can get to the Golden Dawn.
Wow, the Silver Eagles, too.
They all want this guy who came out of nowhere?
Whoa!
They all want him?
Way to show him, you know.
That's my rival for you.
I have to choose the squad that offers me the best path to becoming the Wizard King.
It would be an honor to join the Golden Dawn.
They nabbed the cream of the crop.
That wouldn't have to be awkward.
Well, what can you do?
Next.
Number 165.
The Dark Horse is up.
I've come this far.
I can't let Yuno pull ahead now.
Someone, please pick me.
Do we have any hands?
I don't care which squad.
Raise a hand.
Any hand.
Number 165.
No hands.
It can't be.
Come on, out of the way.
I'm up next.
It's over.
I'm not done.
Not yet.
Have some pride.
I'm not.
There's no real surprise, is it?
Yami?
No matter how great your skill in battle might be, no one wants to touch a power that mysterious.
People aren't fond of the unknown.
It boils down to this.
What the captains are looking for here is magic power.
That's simple.
What's going on?
Hey, what are you doing?
It's like magic is coming off him in waves.
This is it.
It's the power of a magic knight, Captain.
What would anyone ever want with you?
A kid with zero magic.
You might as well face the facts.
What you said before?
That you took the exam because you want to become the Wizard King?
You get what that means, right?
If that's really your goal, you're going to have to prove that you're better than all nine magic knight captains.
And now, standing here magic-less and pathetic, can you really say you have what it takes?
That you're strong enough to be the Wizard King?
Yeah, fine.
So maybe I won't get to join a magic knight squad today.
But no matter what anyone says,
and no matter how many times I might stumble,
I won't give up!
I will become the Wizard King!
You know, kid, I like you.
Come join our crew.
What?
Quit gaping like a fish.
I'm saying I'll let you into the Black Bulls.
By the way, you don't get to say no, got it?
What?
And it won't be a picnic.
We're going to put you through the ringer till you don't recognize yourself.
So get ready.
What?
And then, once we're done, you go and become the Wizard King.
Right!
Number 512, no hands.
Thank you.
This concludes the Magic Knight's entrance exam.
Don't worry!
Don't try and get next to you!
Asta.
You're Golden Dawn, and I'm Black Bulls.
The real battle starts now.
Yeah.
We'll see who...
Grrrr.
Oh, God, is that grilled violent snake I ate earlier coming back for revenge?
It's close! Real close!
Way, way, way too close!
Gotta go, gotta go, gotta go!
You think you can humiliate me and walk away?
Well, I'm going to show you exactly how wrong you are about that, Asta.
Thanks to you, I missed out on the good squads.
I'm stuck in the lower middle ranks with the green praying mantises.
I'm a damn bug.
You think you can come from the back end of nowhere and become the Wizard King?
Idiot.
Sorry, but that's just not how life works.
Bronze curse magic.
Seke's poison lizard.
You got lucky against me, but how about this lizard?
Will your good luck hold?
If not, the best you can hope for is to spend the rest of your life bedridden!
What are you doing?
The poor leaf.
I'm just playing a little joke, that's all.
I thought maybe we could even make a friendly wager.
Just a bet about which one of us will come out on top in the end, you know.
Then get lost.
Go on.
You're not on his level.
Right.
I just remembered, there's something I have to do.
Be sure to give Asta my regards, won't you?
Oh boy, that is so much better.
Ah, everything came out just fine.
Bye-bye, Violet Snake.
Now then, let's go.
You got a lot of nerve making me wait like that, newbie.
Just how long was this dump you took anyway?
Man!
Captain, you wouldn't believe it.
Seriously!
Like, long!
Yeah, and huge too!
That is not what I meant when I asked how long it was.
Like I want to spend my time chatting about your turds, you moron!
Go on, Finral.
Okay.
Whoa, how cool!
What is that?
Obviously, you can't fly on a broom.
So you're going to have to learn some kind of transportation spell to get around.
Oh right, you don't have any magic power.
Um, excuse me, Yami.
This is a pretty sizable gate to keep open for so long.
Could you hurry up and go through already?
It almost sounded like you were telling me what to do.
Suck it up.
Dig deep and push your limits.
Whoa!
In you go.
Ah!
Oh!
Yeah.
Ooh!
Jeez, that hurt.
Ah!
All right!
The Black Bull's hideout!
Nice, huh?
We got a snazzy place.
Mm-hmm.
Crumbling bricks and all.
That's right, home sweet.
As of today, it's going to be my place too.
All right!
I'm the newest member of this squad.
Fresh from Hodge Village.
Awesome!
Whoops.
This is us.
The worst of the worst Magic Knight squads.
Welcome to the Black Bulls.
We'll be right back.
Clover Clips.
Pump it up!
Let's get this party started!
Seke!
That Seke Magnum Cannonball of yours,
could you have chosen a better name?
Ha ha!
And what about your holy lightning rising Salim?
Now that's pure perfection.
Ha ha!
Seke,
I have a feeling that we're going to be great friends.
I did it!
I got a coveted spot on a Magic Knight squad!
The only problem is,
it kind of seems like they're a bunch of crazy people.
Black Clover, page six.
The Black Bulls.
My magic is never giving up!